swirve.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Swirve

Last Updated: August 29th, 2016

Welcome to SWIRVE operated by SWIRVE, LLC (“SWIRVE”, “we”, “us” or “our”). Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect information in relation to our mobile application (the “Service”) and your choices about the collection and use of your information. By using our Service you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to post content, including photos, texts, and instant messaging communications ( **“Content”** ) to the Service and to share this Content publicly. This means that other users may search for, see, use, or share any of your Content that you make publicly available through the Service, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy [http://www.swirve.com/privacypolicy] and our Terms of Use Agreement [http://www.swirve.com/tos]

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully before accessing the Service and creating an account with us. By using the Service you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Our Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service (“ **Users** “). If you disagree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Service.   If you have any questions concerning our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

  1. **Information We Collect About You.**

    1. **Account Information.** We collect information that you provide to us directly such as your email address and login password when you register for a SWIRVE account. If you set up your account using Facebook, you are agreeing to provide us access to information pertaining to your Facebook account including but not limited to your public Facebook profile, email address and information about Facebook friends, and any public information you provide on other social media sites or applications that are linked to your Facebook account, such as Instagram.

    1. **Profile Information** that you provide for your SWIRVE profile such as your unique “Nickname”, birthday, gender, preferences for recommendations by us, such as the distance, age, range and gender, you are interested in viewing profiles of, and any other information you choose to include about yourself, including information you write in your bio, and the photographs and images you post in the Service.

    1. **Other Content** such as photos, comments, content of instant messaging communications if you use the feature to chat with other users, your account activity and history of your use on the site.

    1. **Communications** between you and SWIRVE. For example, we may send you Service-related emails (e.g., account verification, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). Note that you may not opt out of Service-related e-mails. Similarly, if you contact us, we will retain the content of that communication.

In general, we may collect information that can identify you and other information that does not identify you. We may collect this information through the Service. By using the Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse and retain data related to the provision of the Service.

  1. **Log File Information.**

  1. Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access (i.e., visit) a web page or an app. It can also be provided when the content of the webpage or app is downloaded to your browser or device. When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information, including your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

  1. We may also collect similar information from emails that we send to our Users which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.

  1. **Device Identifiers:**

  1. When you use a mobile device to access our Service, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers.” Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device.

  1. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by SWIRVE.

  * A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner about how you browse and use the Service and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

  1. **Metadata:**

  1. Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with your Content. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by whom a piece of your Content was collected and how that Content is formatted.

  1. Users can add or may have Metadata added to their Content by including a hashtag (e.g., to mark keywords when you post a photo), geotag (e.g., to mark your location to a photo), comments or other data. This makes your Content more searchable by others and more interactive. If you geotag your photo or tag your photo using other’s APIs then, your latitude and longitude will be stored with the photo and searchable (e.g., through a location or map feature) if your photo is made public by you in accordance with your privacy settings.

  2. **How We Collect Information About You**.

  1. **Analytics Tools.** We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your device or our Service, including the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User.

  1. **Cookies and Similar Technologies:** When you visit the Service, we may use cookies and similar technologies like pixels, web beacons, and local storage to collect information about how you use SWIRVE and provide features to you. This information could include your IP address, device ID and type, your browser type and language, the operating system used by your device, access times, your mobile device’s geographic location while our application is actively running, and the referring website address. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer Users, to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

  1. **Third Parties** **.** We may allow advertisers or other partners to serve ads or services to your devices, which may use cookies or similar technologies placed by us or the third party. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. We do not provide any non-anonymized personal information to third parties.

  1. **How We Use Your Information.** In addition to the specific uses of your information that we have already described in this Privacy Policy, we may also use your information for the following purposes:

    1. To deliver and improve our products and services, and manage our business;
    2. To manage your account and provide you with customer support;
    3. To perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our or other’s products, services, or content;
    4. To communicate with you about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
    5. To develop, display, and track content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Service and other sites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other sites;
    6. To enforce or exercise any rights in our Terms of Use Agreement [http://www.swirve.com/tos]; and
    7. To perform functions or services as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

  1. **How We Share Your Information.**

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside SWIRVE without your consent, except as noted in this Privacy Policy:

    1. _With Other Users_. By registering with SWIRVE, your profile information will be viewable by other Users of the Service. Other Users will be able to view information you have provided on your profile, including your Nickname and any pictures and text that you post to your profile.

    1. _Your Personal information_. We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated in this Privacy Policy or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with the following parties:

  1. **Service Providers.** We may share your information as well as information from tools like cookies, log files, and device identifiers and location data, with third-party organizations that help us provide the Service to you (“Service Providers”). Our Service Providers will be given access to your information as is reasonably necessary to provide the Service under reasonable confidentiality terms.

  1. **Third Party Advertisers.** We may share certain information such as cookie data with third-party advertising partners. This information would allow third-party ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

  * **Other Parties.** We may remove parts of data that can identify you and share anonymized data with other parties. We may also combine your information with other information in a way that it is no longer associated with you and share that aggregated information. We may also disclose your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. In such instance, every effort will be made by us to ensure that your personal information is disclosed only to those parties or entities that have a legal right and who are bound by obligations of confidentiality and nondisclosure with respect to such information.

  1. **Legal Authorities.** We may be compelled to provide your information in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; we may also do so where we wish to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us: 
    * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing;
    * To protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our Users, our employees, or others;
    * To comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement;
    * To enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements or policies.

  5. **How Long Do We Keep Your Information.** If you disable your account, we will retain certain information associated with your account for a commercially reasonable time for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, enforce our Terms of Use, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our Service or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies. You also may disable your account at any time by visiting the “Settings” page for your account.

  6. **Deleting Your Account.** In order to permanently delete your account from our servers, you must send a deletion request via email to info@swirve.com.

  7. **Choices in How Your Information is Used and Collected.**

  1. If you have a SWIRVE profile, you have the ability to review and update your personal information within the Service by accessing the “Settings” page. More information about how to contact us is provided below. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Service because such information may be required in order for you to register as a User; purchase products or services, or initiate other transactions.

    1. Our Service may also deliver notifications to your mobile device. You can disable these notifications by deleting the relevant Service or by changing the settings on your mobile device.

    1. You can also control information collected by cookies. You can delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. Click “help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.

  1. **How We Protect Your Personal Information.**       We take security measures to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, chats, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid posting personal information such as their full name on their profiles or sending personal information through the Service.

  1. **Information You Provide About Yourself While Using Our Service.** We provide areas on our Service where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use Agreement [http://www.swirve.com/tos]. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other Users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.

  10. **Children’s Privacy**. Although our Service is a general audience Service, we do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under 13, please contact us at info@swirve.com.

  1. **Visiting our Service from outside the United States**. If you are visiting our Service from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States and globally where our servers are located and our central database is operated. By using our services, you understand and agree that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

  1. **No Rights of Third Parties**. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Service.

  1. **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Service from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

  1. **How To Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at info@swirve.com.
